{
    "id": "574ada28492b496a9e12637e1e6cbc75",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The village ................................ I was born is a few hundred miles from here.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdf8f8b5e00845a2b2e59809e0df4f20"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the store in ................................ I used to work.",
            "description": "In which is similar to where. We cannot use that after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a090ea30f50c4dfba55650f721b2c1a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was admired by the people with ............................... he worked.",
            "description": "In a formal style, the preposition comes before the relative pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7594c8c00ba947558d9ea75c5e354a52"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was loved by the people ................................. he worked with.",
            "description": "In an informal style, the preposition goes at the end of the sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9c46e2f7294e44229551f1733e57fe77"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house in .................................... I was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c82847eed60f4fdda69efa79a9946e71"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the room .................................... I was born in.",
            "description": "That is used when the preposition goes at the end. It cannot be used after a preposition. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c81be80c2d324e319c074d7b85a5e2cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know ................................. she is from.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7b75be10ef024905a3e50c826a56e5dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know ................................ country she is from?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5fc8a01d471d4c4490fadd2525ccd46f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He always quarreled with the people with ................................... he worked.",
            "description": "We cannot use who and that after prepositions.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72ed3ce194674f76aa148a58f3cdf8c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know …………………………. I met at the club yesterday?",
            "description": "In an informal style who is also possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75f2874ba46a4d6a81ec3f930491d14a"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she said made me angry.",
            "description": "What means the things which.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7cfddbe65a24f67b3e2c7dc577677c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should give me …………………………. I want.",
            "description": "What means the things which.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d20e0bd06003447fbd538cb7b4652fbb"
        }
    ]
}